<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="interview_questions">How to Prepare for the 10 Most Common Interview Questions</string>
    <string name="before_any_interview">Would you like to feel confident and well prepared before any interview?</string>
    <string name="every_company_s_interview">While every company is different and their interview processes unique, there are some common interview questions that you are likely to be asked in almost every company\'s interview.</string>
    <string name="your_profile_and_personality">There are also general tips and ways of preparing for these interview questions, which are our recommendations of how best to answer these questions. However, you should definitely personalize these sample responses according to your profile and personality.</string>
    <string name="pieces_of_general_advice">Before getting into the details of showing you answers to the above questions, a few pieces of general advice:</string>
    <string name="learning_opportunity_for_you">Whenever you talk about past experiences or examples from your personal life, don\'t focus on the negative aspects of those experiences. Instead talk about how all your experiences, whether good or bad, were a great learning opportunity for you.</string>
    <string name="keep_your_mind_at_ease">Besides, some companies invest time and resources to perform background checks of potential employees. So rather than worrying about a falsified story or claim being cross checked with a reference, be honest and keep your mind at ease. ;</string>
    <string name="services_the_company_offers">Go through their company website – you should at least know what the company does. Read about what are the core products or services the company offers.</string>
    <string name="you_make_a_good_impression">If possible, go through their Vision, Mission or Values statements – if you use them in your answers, it helps you make a good impression.</string>
    <string name="good_fit_for_their_requirements">Last but definitely not the least, read about the Job Description and the Requirements for the position that you are applying for thoroughly. Basically, find out what your potiential employer wants, and in the interview, show them how you are a good fit for their requirements.</string>
    <string name="requirements_that_the_company_has">Once you have presented your basic information, go into the details of how your skills, qualifications and experience are quite relevant for the requirements that the company has.</string>
    <string name="working_on_fixing_it">2. Explain how you have identified the weakness and are working on fixing it</string>
    <string name="improving_yourself">This will help to demonstrate that not only are you humble enough to admit you have a weakness, but you also are motivated enough to keep improving yourself.</string>
    <string name="answer_beforehand">Remember at all times try to make your response sound as authentic and honest as possible. You will be able to do this only if you prepare and memorize your answer beforehand.</string>
    <string name="other_people_or_yourself">Never say anything negative about your previous industry, company, board, boss, staff, employees or customers. Be honest while answering this question but frame it in such a way that you don’t sound like you’re only blaming other people or yourself.</string>
    <string name="answer_this_question_is">Instead have a positive approach to this question, some of the ways you can answer this question is:</string>
    <string name="current_previous_position">1. You want to learn some specific skills or gain some specific experience that you are unable to at the current / previous position</string>
    <string name="professionalism_and_maturity">Instead, explain how you could understand why it happened, from the company’s point-of-view, and you have no bitter feelings about it. This presents an impression of great professionalism and maturity.</string>
    <string name="any_other_candidate">There are several strategies of answering this question. However, it is critical to identify what the company’s needs and expectations are from a potential hire. Only when you know what they want, can you effectively answer this question better than any other candidate.</string>
    <string name="going_for_the_interview">This question tests whether you’ve done any homework about the company or not. Like we have mentioned before, read about the company, their website, their services, their Vision, Mission and Values statements thoroughly before going for the interview.</string>
    <string name="them_resolved_effectively">I think I am a very good fit for this role because I have worked as a Customer Service Executive for 2 years. Thanks to the training that I received along with my experience of handling over 120 customer grievances every week, I am confident that I will be able to understand your customers’ issues and get them resolved effectively.</string>
    <string name="part_of_the_effort">1. You are excited about the products and services that the firm is working on and you want to be a part of the effort</string>
    <string name="want_to_contribute">2. You are inspired by the Vision and the Mission of the firm to make an impact, and want to contribute</string>
    <string name="positions_of_management">This is a question that is usually asked for candidates applying for senior positions, or positions of management.</string>
    <string name="your_answer_believable">This is an easy question and the obvious answer you would want to give is Yes. But make your answer believable.</string>
    <string name="asking_this_question">Candidates who are appearing for interview while having prior experience will commonly be asked this question. However before you answer it, what you should realize is the intent behind asking this question.</string>
    <string name="intention_usually_is_to_find_out">Your interviewer will not ask you this question just to hear about your story, but the intention usually is to find out:</string>
    <string name="your_performance">Once you have realized these intentions, focus your answer to talk about these aspects only – Your expertise or skills, your responsibilities and your performance.</string>
    <string name="perform_much_better">You will almost always join a team within the new company. So interviewers usually want to make sure that you are a good team player and will get along well with others. In general, teams where individuals put the interests of the team before themselves, tend to perform much better.</string>
    <string name="perform_better_as_a_whole">Talk about how you faced a situation where you kept your own interests, or ego or opinions aside, and that helped the team to actually perform better as a whole.</string>
    <string name="prepared_and_stay_positive">These are some of the basic interview questions that are commonly asked by a lot of companies across industries. We hope this list of suggestions on how to answer them was helpful. Remember to stay confident, stay prepared and stay positive.</string>
    <string name="handled_pressure_well">Think of a story or incident that you can provide as an example of times when you handled pressure well.</string>
    <string name="cultivate_your_skills_etc">4. You think this company is the best place to learn, grow and cultivate your skills etc.</string>
    <string name="the_company_offers">3. You are looking forward to be a part of the excellent work culture the company offers</string>
    <string name="ability_to_do_the_job">It\'s important to prepare well for this question and respond carefully. You don\'t want to cast any doubt on your ability to do the job.</string>
    <string name="the_employer_s_requirements">1. A proven track record as an achiever – especially if your achievements match up with the employer\'s requirements</string>
    <string name="their_employees_are">As a general guideline, some of the most desirable traits that all employers love to see in their employees are:</string>
    <string name="impressive_achievements">You should have one or two specific examples for each strength, chosen from your most recent and most impressive achievements.</string>
    <string name="your_greatest_strengths">This question is an opportunity for you to present your best self. Prior to any interview, you should have a list mentally prepared of your greatest strengths.</string>
    <string name="relevant_for_this_position">It saves a lot of time if you focus only on those skills or experiences that are relevant for this position.</string>
    <string name="in_this_profile">Another way to answer this question is to follow-up your introduction with a question to understand what is the interviewer exactly looking for in this profile?.</string>
    <string name="common_interview_questions">10 Common Interview Questions:</string>
    <string name="_1_tell_me_about_yourself">1. Tell me about yourself</string>
    <string name="greatest_strengths">2. What are your greatest strengths?</string>
    <string name="leave_this_position">4. Why are you leaving (or did you leave) this position?</string>
    <string name="at_our_company">6. Why do you want to work at our company?</string>
    <string name="on_board">7. What changes would you make if you came on board?</string>
    <string name="the_last_company">9. Tell me about your work in the last company</string>
    <string name="team_spirit">10. Give me an example where you showed good team spirit</string>
    <string name="body_language">Pay attention to your body language</string>
    <string name="wear_for_women">1. Dress well (Business formals for men and Formals or Indian ehtnic wear for women)</string>
    <string name="whenever_appropriate">5. Try to maintain eye contact whenever appropriate</string>
    <string name="company_and_role">Read about the company and role</string>
    <string name="now_let_s_get_into_the_10_common_interview_questions">Now, let\'s get into the details of answering the 10 common interview questions:</string>
    <string name="answering_this_question">Below is a basic framework of answering this question:</string>
    <string name="answers_for_this_question">And these are a few sample answers for this question:</string>
    <string name="applying_for_will_help">This is where your homework about the company and the role that you are applying for will help.</string>
    <string name="decent_human_being">2. Honesty and integrity – basically a decent human being</string>
    <string name="well_in_the_company">3. A team player who fits well in the company</string>
    <string name="achieve_excellence">6. Dedication – willingness to take extra efforts to achieve excellence</string>
    <string name="high_levels_of_motivation">8. Enthusiasm – high levels of motivation</string>
    <string name="leadership_skills">9.Confidence, and leadership skills</string>
    <string name="have_any_weaknesses">However, you also don’t want to seem arrogant or dishonest by saying that you don’t have any weaknesses.</string>
    <string name="are_applying_for">1. Pick a weakness that is not critical to the job you are applying for</string>
    <string name="prepare_for_this_question">Below is a great video on how to prepare for this question:</string>
    <string name="financially_or_professionally">3. You want an opportunity to grow, either financially or professionally</string>
    <string name="entirely_new_skill_set_etc">4. You want to expand your horizons and learn an entirely new skill set etc.</string>
    <string name="you_left_the_position">For every position in your past experience prepare a brief reason on why you left the position.</string>
    <string name="handle_their_issues">A person who can politely talk to customers and handle their issues</string>
    <string name="have_the_highest_impact">1. List down the top two to three items that you think will have the highest impact</string>
    <string name="timelines_for_your_actions">3. If possible list down costs and timelines for your actions</string>
    <string name="about_tackling_them">2. List down ideas or actions on how you would go about tackling them</string>
    <string name="whenever_possible">4. Give examples from your past experience or training whenever possible</string>
    <string name="question_is_asked">Memorize this answer so that you can use it whenever such a question is asked.</string>
    <string name="this_role_well">2. What were your responsibilities there, and will you fill in the responsibilities for this role well?</string>
    <string name="well_for_this_role_etc">3. How was your performance in the last role and will you perform well for this role? Etc.</string>
    <string name="recent_and_relevant">So the key to answering it effectively is by quoting an example that is recent and relevant.</string>
    <string name="jobs_on_just_jobs_hr">Once you feel equipped to appear for interviews, you can start looking for jobs on Just Jobs HR.</string>
    <string name="good_team_spirit">10. Give me an example where you showed good team spirit</string>
    <string name="their_requirements_are">1. Was your recent experience relevant to what their requirements are?</string>
    <string name="came_on_board">7. What changes would you make if you came on board?</string>
    <string name="can_mention_are_how">Some of the reasons that you can mention are, How:</string>
    <string name="work_at_our_company">6. Why do you want to work at our company?</string>
    <string name="reason_for_hiring_you">Possible Reason for hiring you:</string>
    <string name="why_should_i_hire_you">5. Why should I hire you?</string>
    <string name="position_don_t_lie_about_it">If you did get fired from the previous position, don’t lie about it.</string>
    <string name="this_question_positively_is">A good way to this answer this question positively is:</string>
    <string name="positive_attitude">4. Positive attitude</string>
    <string name="sit_upright">2. Sit upright</string>
    <string name="positive_and_confident">Be positive and confident</string>
    <string name="your_greatest_weaknesses">3. What are your greatest weaknesses?</string>
    <string name="attitude_always_helps">Always be confident when appearing for interviews. An optimistic and positive attitude always helps.</string>
    <string name="work_that_you_deliver">It never helps to present a false picture of who you are or what your skills and experiences are. Apart from the fact that people appreciate honest, sincere individuals in an interview, setting the wrong expectations might land you the job, but your true skill and effectiveness will only show in the work that you deliver.</string>
    <string name="going_for_any_interview">It essential to do your homework about the company and the specific role you are applying for, before going for any interview.</string>
    <string name="hands_confidently">4.Shake hands confidently</string>

</resources>